But otherwise the Finnish economy has been bleak.
A bit like elsewhere too.
Everything that happens with industrial production, growth, the prospects has been quite weak.
But you still see resilience during the latter part of the year.
What are you saying?
If we look at individual companies, they are starting to be very cheaply priced.
Finland has had two years of downward stock prices.
At the same time, the companies' situation is not completely hopeless.
Next year, we expect a profit growth of 5-7 % if we look at index level.
And at the same time, these companies are very cheap.
So if you look a little longer you should own the Finnish stock exchange as well.
Could it be a good position to come in if you don't have ...?
Not getting in at the top is always nice.
Fed has done its thing, the ECB has probably done its thing.
At the same time we see that the growth figures are getting a little lower-
-in the start of next year.
If it becomes a "soft landing" in the US, we will see ...
But clearly lower growth.
And it is already priced that the policy rates will be lower in 2024.
It should stimulate the economy to some extent.
You started working in the financial market before 1992.
You are a bit back in a world with a lot of uncertainty-
-But where interest rates are also interesting again.
-Just.
-Do you other synergies?
That's right.
In 1992 I started as an interest portfolio manager in a Finnish company-
And though the policy rate drops so ...
There are so much loans that need to be financed again-
-So it may be that the risk premium, the price they have to pay for new loan-
-will rise.
But can't it be that you now get in at the top?
That those who allocate about their portfolios, that they invest errors at the top in the interest rate market-
-and that they get a lower return.
Isn't that risk?
As an investor, if you have a little longer horizon and place in corporate loans ...
Then this is a great buying position.
But for companies ... we had an example here in Finland.
A medium-sized company in the construction industry that in 2021 had borrowed money-